Now listen, yo!
People put your guns up
Mazu ore ga run dat
Hashirimawatte yatsura o gun shot
Brand new sound sou still survival
Here come the sound boy kono sekai ni ikiro
Chiryoku tairyoku to un ga mau ze! Flow
Fukuranda ataman naka wa zakkubaran nan da
Savannah de Banna ni wanpan
Kantan knockout kan kan kan
One time for your mind ikinuke
Around the world
Tsukimatou no sa itsu no itami mo
Kedakai kami no mawari mo ima karimono
Makareta tane mo hana sakeba dare no
Ikite uchikomu shinnen no ya o more more more
Ikisaki ni yasuragi wa nai
Tachi na sa don't give up the fight
Ima sou kono shunkan mo die die die
Big shooter ikiisoide blazing
Beat you up kirihiraite break
Shot shooter ikiisoida crazy
Shoujun au shikin kyori de break
Big shooter ikiisoide blazing
Beat you up kirihiraite break
Shot shooter ikiisoida crazy
Shoujun au shikin kyori de break
A week has already passed since
Ratenin temple,
（リポーター）この閑静な
住宅街にある羅鼎院(らていいん)が―
located in this quiet neighborhood,
突如
何者かによって破壊されてから―
既に２週間が経過しましたが―
was suddenly destroyed by unknown means.
According to police statements,
警視庁の発表によりますと
依然 原因は不明とのことです
the details behind this incident remain unclear,
with the only lead at this point being
唯一の手がかりは
境内の裏手で発見された―
the bodies of two homeless men found behind
and in close proximity to the temple.
２人のホームレスの
遺体なのですが…
（計(けい)）あっ…
Wait for me!
（男の子）待ってよ！
Kishimoto
Don't Ever Say That Again!
Hey!
（女性）ねえ お茶飲もう
Let's drink tea!
So...
（岸本(きしもと)）だから あの子が これから
どうするのか分からないけど―
So I don't know what she's going
to do from now on,
私は 私の生き方をしてみるんだ
but I'm going to try to live my own life.
Hey! How many times do I have to tell you?
（古田(ふるた)）
おい 何度言ったら分かる？
Hey, wait!
待て こら！
Labyrinth
み… 見ないでよ
Don't look...
（佳乃(よしの)）アアッ…
Somebody! Help me!
（学(まなぶ)の母親）誰か！ 助けて！
（学）アアッ…
（学の母親）学！
Manabu!
（学）アアッ…
（母親）学ちゃん！
Manabu!
Somebody help us!
（母親）誰か助けて！
（斉藤(さいとう)）ハァハァ…
（お金の落ちる音）
（斉藤）あっ… くそ… あっ…
Damn!
（斉藤）あっ…
（男性）ウワッ…
SELL YOUR KIDNEYAND
GIVE BACK THE MONEY
FLESRUOY LLIK NEHT DNA
ECNARUSNI EFIL EMOS TEG
（駅員）おい ちょっと… ウワッ！
Hey, you there!
It's the beginning of a brand new day...
（殴る音）
（梶浦(かじうら)）ハハハハッ… 殺すなよ
Don't kill her, all right?
We won't be able to make any money off of her.
（梶浦）
さすがに売れなくなるからな
This bitch is already useless.
（室戸）この女 もう使えねえよ
次の家出娘 探すか
Guess we'll have to go find
ourselves a new runaway girl, huh?
Oh, shit!
（梶浦）やべえ！
Let's go pick up that book together, okay?
（聖(せい)）本 一緒に取りに行こうね！
I can do it! And we can go home!
（聖）いける　帰れる
Together...
一緒に 帰れるよ！
We can go home!
（野崎(のざき)）ンンッ…
Manabu!
（母親）学！
Give... Give me a hand!
（野崎）手… 手を…
Manabu!
（母親）学…
（野崎）ンンッ…
あっ！ ウワッ！
Like I said, there's nothing
you can do about that.
（女性）だから それはね
しかたないでしょう
You have to think more about other people.
もっと他人のこと考えなきゃダメよ
Hey, watch out!
（古田）おい 危ないぞ！ おい！
Hey!
The train will soon be arriving at platform 2.
（アナウンス）２番線に電車が…
Please stay behind the white line.
（取り立て屋）て… てめえ…
You... You son of a bitch!
You think you can get away from us?!
（取り立て屋）
逃げられると思うな！
Gantz always attacks us in ways
we can't predict.
（加藤(かとう)）ガンツは いつも
予想のつかない攻撃を仕掛けてくる
But we have to fight off ALL its attacks...
でも それを全て撃退しなければ
生き残ることはできない
or we'll never be able to survive.
Here comes another one!
またですよ
（古田）あっ…
You're...
（古田）君…
（計）えっ？ あっ…
I saw you earlier this evening...
君 さっき… ほら 夕方
Let's see... Miranda Foster's "Labyrinth."
（古田）え～っと…
ミランダ・フォスターの―
「迷宮」っとね…
Oh, here it is.
ああ これだ
But you're not the one who
placed this order, are you?
あれ この本…
君が注文したんじゃないよね？
Sei Sakuraoka did.
桜丘(さくらおか)聖さん …です
Why are you picking it up?
どうして 君が取りに来たの？
友達？
（計）あっ えっと…
Is she your friend?
Well, um...
If we do make it back alive,
you wanna go out with me?
（聖）生きて戻れたらさ
私たち つきあわない？
Yeah. She is...
はぁ… 友達…
Promise me...
約束だよ
my friend.
…です
（聖）
来週 届くんだ　駅前の本屋さん
It's supposed to come in next week.
At the bookstore by the train station.
計君
私 どうなるか分からないから―
Kei, I don't know what's
going to happen to me...
But if anything does, would you
go get that book for me?
そうなったら
取りに行ってくれないかな？
If by any chance I...
You know what I mean, right?
“万が一”ってやつ
いいでしょう？
Is that okay with you?
Furuta Books
Has it come in yet?
（計）届いてますか？
I'm sorry. We're supposed to
get it in tomorrow.
（古田）
ごめんね あした届く予定なんだよ
Oh. Okay...
（計）そうですか…
Also, our policy is that
we can't give it to you
（古田）それに
一応 本人に確認してみないと―
渡せない決まりになっててね
unless we check with the one
who ordered it first.
It's not like I don't trust you, though...
ああ 別に君を
疑ってるわけじゃないんだけどね
I'm going to call Miss Sakuraoka
right now. Hold on a second.
今 桜丘さんに電話してみるから
ちょっと待ってて
Excuse me.
あの…
（古田）うん？
Yes?
I don't think you'll be able to
get through to her...
電話 多分
つながらないと思いますんで…
じゃ いいです
So never mind.
You're...
（古田）君…
（佳乃）ねえ 君…
Hey, you're... Kurono, aren't you?
玄野(くろの)君よね？
（計）あっ…
I didn't know she died...
（計）先生 死んだんだ…
What are you doing here?
こんなとこで何してるの？
その格好…
And that outfit...
説明しても分かんないよ 多分
I doubt you'd understand... even if I did explain.
…てことは 何か知ってるの？
So you DO know what's going on?
Miss Uehara...
先生
You were having an affair, weren't you?
不倫してたよね？
え… えっ？
ちょっと 玄野君 何言ってるの？
Huh? What?
Who do you think you are, Kurono?!
That's not what I'm talking about.
Now tell me what's going on!
そうじゃなくて
一体 何が どうなって…
Like I said, it's hard to explain...
（計）
だから 説明って言われても…
Hm?
（みか）あれ？ あの子 どこかで…
I think I've seen him somewhere before...
It looks like it stopped raining,
so why don't we get out of here?
（梶浦）雨 やんだみたいだし―
こんなとこ出ましょうよ
（計）あっ…
What do you say, everyone?
ねっ？ 皆さん
（室戸）こんなとこ出ましょうよ
No point in hanging around a place like this.
It's them!
（計）あいつらだ
なんで ここに？
Why are they here?
But why did THIS have to happen?!
（加藤）
こんなのって ありなのかよ？
How can it be okay to kill someone
just because he's homeless?!
（加藤）ホームレスだからって
殺していいのかよ？
What kind of a world are we
trying to get back to?!
俺たちが帰ろうとしてるのは
どういう世界なんだよ？
（計）加藤 こいつら まだ生きてる
Kato...
These bastards are still alive!
No. They may be dead,
（計）
いや 死んだかもしんねえけど―
but they're standing in front of me right now!
今 俺の前に いるぜ！
Kishimoto...
岸本が…
岸本が死んだっつうのに…
How can Kishimoto be dead
but THEY are still here?!
なんで こいつらが
まだ ここにいるんだよ？
Hey... Wait!
あの… ちょ… 待って！
What is it?
（岸本）何ですか？
Well, um, I've never done this before, but...
あ… あの… こんなの初めてで…
Um... It's, like, you're my type, so...
あの… 好みっつうか…
（計）あっ… 待って！
Wait!
Are you hitting on me?
ナンパ？
（計）あっ… いや…
Well, uh, I don't usually
do stuff like this. I mean...
でも ふだん こんなことしない
つうか…
Your name.
（岸本）名前…
（計）あっ…
What's your name?
何ていうの？
（計）えっ？ ああ… 玄野
Kurono. It's Kei Kurono.
玄野計
（岸本）ケイ？
Kei?
Yeah! Same as yours, right?
そう 同じだよね？
えっ？ なんで…
How...
How do you know my name is Kei?
なんで
私の名前 ケイだって知ってるの？
（計）あっ…
（岸本）私の名字は？
Do you know my last name, too?
（計）岸本…
Kishimoto.
Hey, wait!
（計）あっ… 待って！
Mom! Mom!
（岸本）お母さん！ お母さん！
（計）待って！
Wait!
君は一緒に暮らしてた子に
そっくりなんだ
You look exactly like a girl
I used to live with!
俺のアパートで一緒に暮らしてた
She used to stay with me at my apartment.
She was sweet and...
and I really liked her. But...
優しくて す… 好きだった
でも…
She died.
死んじゃったんだ
Do I look that much like her?
そんなに似てたの？
And we have the same name, too?
名前も同じで…
How is that even possible?!
（岸本）そんなわけないじゃん
気持ちわるっ！
That's just creepy!
I guess she's right.
…だよな
It does sound creepy.
確かに 気持ち悪いよな
Kurono!
（佳乃）玄野君
（計）あっ…
If you know something, explain it to us now.
知ってることがあるなら
みんなに説明して
あっ 私の不倫のことじゃなくてよ
And I DON'T mean my affair.
I don't know if I can explain it
as well as Kato did.
（計）
加藤みたいに うまくできっかな？
Well, that black ball right there
is about to open,
あ～… え～っと…
これから そこの黒い玉が開いて
武器が出てくるんだ
and some weapons are going to come out of it.
Weapons?
（斉藤）武器？
（古田）何だ？ それは
What do you mean?
（計）銃…
（室戸）あっ…
Guns.
（室戸）ほ… 本物のですか？
（計）ああ
Real ones?
Yeah.
What are you talking about, Kurono?
（佳乃）玄野君 何言ってるの？
そんな荒唐無稽(こうとうむけい)な…
That's just ridiculous...
Next, it'll tell us to kill some aliens,
so we go out and kill them.
（計）それから “何とか星人を
殺せ”っていうのが出て―
そいつらを倒しに行く
（斉藤）はぁ？
Huh?
Jeez. Give me a break.
（梶浦）
やれやれ 困ったもんですな
Talk about having an imagination...
妄想というか何というか
（室戸）へえ
Hey, sorry to interrupt,
but we need to be going home.
君 悪いが 私たちは
早く家に帰らなきゃならないんだよ
I'm not lying!
（計）ウソじゃない
そうしないと みんな死ぬ
And if we don't kill them,
we're all going to die!
Hey, that's what I wanted to ask!
それですよ それ！
Um, didn't we all just die earlier?
あの… 私たち
さっき 死にませんでしたか？
But no matter how look at it, we're alive now.
しかし
今の私らは どう見ても生きてる
You can even see the Tokyo Tower!
（野崎）東京タワーも見えるぜ
That's right. It's difficult to believe we're dead.
そうね
とても 死んだなんて思えないわ
Kurono, what's really going on?
（佳乃）
玄野君 ホントのところ どうなの？
Like I said...
だから…
くそ！
Dammit, Kato! I'm not good at this kind of stuff!
加藤 俺 こういうの苦手だ
どうすりゃいいんだよ？
What should I do?
Look, why don't we just
introduce ourselves for now?
（古田）ひとまず １人ずつ
自己紹介したら どうだろう？
それと 各人 どうやって死んだとか
その辺の事情を…
We could also explain how we died...
The circumstances and so forth.
We might be able to figure something out, right?
そしたら
何か分かるかもしれないだろう？
I'll go first.
じゃ 私から
I'm Giichi Furuta, 50 years old.
古田義一(ぎいち) 50歳
駅前で本屋をしています
I run a bookstore by the train station.
I died by...
死因は…
（野崎）ホントに死んだのか？
But did you really die?
I died by...
I don't know! That's why we're
trying to find out the truth!
分からんよ！ だから その真相を
探ろうっていうんじゃないか
I died in a car accident.
（古田）死因は交通事故
I was hit by a car while chasing
after a shoplifter.
万引きした少年を追いかけていて
車に やられました
Okay, next is...
え～っと 次は… じゃ あなた
How about you?
Me?
え… えっ？ 私？
This is only to find out the truth, so
you don't need to go into any details.
真相究明のためですから―
差し障りのない程度で結構ですので
Yoshino Uehara, 26 years old.
上原(うえはら)佳乃 26歳
C'mon, don't lie! You're 29, aren't you?
（計）サバ読むなよ 29だろう
I teach high school.
（佳乃）高校の教師をしています
彼の担任です
I'm his homeroom teacher.
Oh, and his name is Kurono.
He's in the 10th grade.
ああ 彼は玄野君　高校１年生です
（古田）…で 死因は？
And? How did you die?
Well... That's, um...
えっ？ ちょ… ちょっと その…
I got stabbed and...
刺されちゃいまして
（みか）あっ…
That's really all I can say.
（佳乃）それ以上は ちょっと…
Was that maybe because of the affair?
あっ…
もしかして 不倫の もつれ？
Daichi Nozaki. I fell into a river.
野崎大地(だいち)　川に落ちた
How old are you?
（古田）歳は？
（野崎）17　無職
Seventeen. And I'm unemployed.
Aren't you going to school?
学校は行ってないの？
（野崎）関係ねえだろう！
That's none of your business, is it?!
Ryuji Kajiura, 28 years old.
I do odd jobs here and there.
梶浦龍二(りゅうじ) 28
仕事は まあ いろいろと
He's Hajime Muroto, 16 years old.
こいつは室戸一(はじめ) 16
I'm taking care of him.
私が面倒を見ています
保護者ですかね
I guess you could say I'm his guardian.
み… 皆さん よろしく
Nice to meet you all.
（計）俺と同じ歳かよ
He's the same age as me?!
I died in an accident... A car accident.
（室戸）死因は事故です　交通事故
The same as me, huh?
あっ 私と同じだね
Do you think there's some kind of connection?
何か関係あります？
（古田）う～ん…
Well...
Um, can I say something?
（みか）あの… いいですか？
（古田）はい どうぞ
Go ahead.
I've got the feeling that maybe
we really are dead.
やっぱり 私たち ホントに
死んでるんじゃないかと思ってて
For months, I was being followed
by some kind of stalker.
私 何か月もストーカーっぽい人に
追い回されてて
He just stabbed me a little while ago...
さっき その人に刺されて…
He came at me with a knife.
I fought back as hard as I could, but...
（みか）ナイフで襲われて
必死になって抵抗したんですけど
This book.
これ そのとき…
（斉藤・古田）あっ…
（みか）そのとき―
His knife went through this book
when he stabbed me.
この本も一緒に刺されちゃって
It's almost like proof.
証拠っていうか
なぜか この本だけなんだけど…
I know it's just a book, but...
But if I'm not dead, why would I be
carrying something like this around?
でも 死んでないんなら
どうして こんなの持ってるのか…
あっ… 私 神田(かんだ)みかです
短大生 二十歳です
Oh, and I'm Mika Kanda.
I'm a college student, 20 years old.
あ～… じゃ
今のところ 交通事故が２人
Okay, that makes two... no, three car accidents,
いやいやいや ３人だ
two stabbings,
え～… 刺されたのが２人
and one drowning.
溺死が１人
I guess car accidents and stabbings
are connected somehow...
事故と刺されたのは
何か関係があんのかな？
What about you, Kurono?
How did you end up here?
（佳乃）
玄野君は？ どうして ここに？
It was a while ago, but I
got hit by a subway train.
（計）だいぶ前だけど
地下鉄に はねられて
Come on now. You've been
coming to school every day!
あのね あなた
毎日 学校に来てたじゃない？
You can't be serious.
そんなことあるわけないでしょう
（計）ホントだって
It's the truth!
I said you wouldn't understand!
だから “言っても信じない”って
さっき…
（斉藤）あの…
Excuse me...
Actually, I jumped in front of a subway train.
私 実は地下鉄に飛び込みまして…
（計）あっ…
あっ 私 斉藤直純(なおずみ)といいます
38になったばかりです
My name is Naozumi Saito. I just turned 38.
Up until last year, I was working
for a major bank...
去年まで大手の銀行に
勤めていたんですが その…
Well, it's sort of an embarrassing story,
お恥ずかしい話ですが
リストラに遭いまして
but I ended up losing my job through
corporate restructuring.
事業を起こしたものの
借金が増えて―
I started my own business, but
I fell deeper and deeper into debt.
取り立て屋に追われちゃいましてね
I was being hounded by bill collectors,
and I jumped off the train platform.
思わず地下鉄のホームから
電車に飛び込んだ次第でして
But since I've been here, I mean,
aside from what's really happening,
ただ ここに来てみたら
真相は ともかくとして―
I feel sort of relieved.
何だかホッとしたというか
I find myself thinking, "Finally! I don't need
to be chased by those bill collectors anymore!"
“ああ これで もう借金取りに
追われることもないんだな”
…なんて思ってしまって
Surprisingly, I feel pretty calm right now.
（斉藤）
今は不思議と穏やかな気分でして…
えっ？ オッ…
（計）おい 笑ってんじゃねえよ
Hey! Wipe that smile off your face!
What?
ちょ… ちょっと…
You feel CALM? Don't give me that crap!
穏やかな気分？ ふざけんな！
What? What are you doing?
（斉藤）な… 何なんですか？
（古田）君… 玄野君 やめなさい！
You, Kurono! Stop it!
ウワッ…
（斉藤）アア…
（斉藤）アアッ…
（佳乃）乱暴は やめなさい 玄野君
Stop being so violent, Kurono!
You... You killed yourself, didn't you?
あんた それって自殺だろう？
（斉藤）は… はい そうです
Yes, I did.
So many... So many people have died here!
You wouldn't believe how many.
何人も何人も死んだ！
すげえ人数なんだ
Some of them came here after
killing themselves first,
中には 自殺して
ここに来たヤツも いたさ
but they all tried to go back!
けどな みんな帰ろうとしたんだよ
They tried to go back somehow...
Tried to break free from this place!
なんとかして
ここから自由になろうとして…
But they couldn't make it. They all died!
それでもダメで
どんどん死んでいったんだ！
"You feel calm."
穏やかだなんて
二度と言うな！ 分かったか？
Don't ever say that again! You got that?!
す… すみません
I... I'm sorry.
Whether you believe it or not,
（計）信じようが信じまいが
もうすぐ ひどい殺し合いが始まる
a terrible massacre is about to begin.
And when it does, I guarantee you
that some of us are going to die!
そうなったら
この中の何人かは確実に死ぬんだ
I thought we were already dead.
もう死んでんじゃねえのかよ？
（計）うるさい！ 人の話を聞け！
Shut up! Listen to what I have to say!
If you want to survive, you have to
prepare yourselves.
生き残りたいヤツは
覚悟を決めてくれ
そうじゃなきゃ
俺だって助けようがない！
Even I can't help you unless you do!
I understand. We just have to do
what you say, right?
分かったわ
玄野君の指示に従えばいいのね？
（計）あっ… ああ… まあ
Uh, yeah...
確かに　よくは分からないが―
I certainly don't understand it all,
but I don't think he's making it up.
彼がウソを言っているとも
思えないな
Okay, Kurono. I'm not saying I believe all this,
but I'll ask you this just in case:
…で 玄野君 まだ完全に
信じたわけじゃないが 念のため
What's going to happen next?
次は どうなるんだい？
Let's see, first...
（計）え～っと まず…
It's the beginning of a brand new day
Your lives are now over,
you bastards.
It's the beginning of a brand new day
Your lives are now over,
you bastards.
A day filled with hope
Your lives are now over,
you bastards.
What you do with
A day filled with hope
Your lives are now over,
you bastards.
What you do with
your new lives
A day filled with hope
Your lives are now over,
you bastards.
What you do with
your new lives
is for me to decide.
A day filled with hope
Your lives are now over,
you bastards.
What you do with
your new lives
is for me to decide.
So there you have it.
A day filled with hope
Open your heart to happiness
Gantz! What alien is it this time?
（計）ガンツ 今度は何星人だ？
And look up at the big, blue sky
No matter what you bring on, I'll fuckin' kill it!
何を出してこようが
ぶっつぶしてやる！
No matter what you bring on, I'll fuckin' kill it!
Listen to the voice on the radio
Come on! Show me!
さあ 見せてみろ！
Your lives are now over,
you bastards.
What you do with
your new lives
is for me to decide.
So there you have it.
Listen to the voice on the radio
Please go eliminate
What alien is it?
Listen to the voice on the radio
（計）何星人だ！
Please go eliminate
What alien is it?
And fill your lungs
Please go eliminate
this target now,
What alien is it?
And fill your lungs
Please go eliminate
this target now,
you bastards.
What alien is it?
And fill your lungs
Please go eliminate
this target now,
you bastards.
And fill your lungs
...now, you bastards.
Kurono Alien
And fill your lungs
...now, you bastards.
Kurono Alien
With the fragrant air
One! Two! Three! Let's go!
No way!
マジかよ？
お… 俺？
Kurono Alien
Characteristics:
Kinda strong, Horny
Special Skills:
Getting a Hard-on
Likes:
Big breasts, Gun battles
Catch Phrase:
I'll kill you!
I'll fuckin' kill you!
Kurono Alien
Characteristics:
Kinda strong, Horny
Special Skills:
Getting a Hard-on
Likes:
Big breasts, Gun battles
Catch Phrase:
I'll kill you!
I'll fuckin' kill you!
Kurono Alien
Characteristics:
Kinda strong, Horny
Special Skills:
Getting a Hard-on
Likes:
Big breasts, Gun battles
Catch Phrase:
I'll kill you!
I'll fuckin' kill you!
Hajimari wa dare demo junshin muku na baby
Nigai mi kajitte mo kujikecha
dame yo walk straight
Satta koto da kedo ame no naka
zukizuki itamu yo
I'm lonely as floating ice
Yaseta yubi ni kiss o shite
Naita anata o omoidasu yo
Kore de owari da to shite mo
Saigo no kiss wa wasurenai yo
Wasurenai yo
Kare no kiss o wasurenai yo
（梶浦）別に何も
悪いことなんかしてないんですよ
It's not like he's done anything bad...
It's just, it looks like we won't be able to
go home unless we kill him. Right?
ただね あいつをやらないと
帰れないみたいだから　ねっ？
Next episode,
次回 “玄野星人！”
"Kurono Alien!"